tots100.co.uk 2017-07-11

# Privacy & Cookies | Tots 100

Tots100 and [Flea Enterprises](http://www.fleaenterprises.com/) are committed to protecting your privacy and security. From time to time we may ask you to supply personal information on this site to help us provide you with services, such as setting up a blog profile or a PR agency subscription, or subscribing to our email newsletters and competitions.

In order to deliver such services, we may store and process personal information. By submitting this information, you consent to such processing in connection with your Tots100/Flea Enterprises account, offers and services. We may contact you from time to time with information about your account, and important changes to our website and services.

Subject to the terms below, we will not share your personal details with any third party without your consent. We may provide aggregate information about users, statistics, traffic patterns and site information to our partners, but we will never share any information from which you might be identified without your consent.

If you enter a competition on our website, we may share contact details with the promoters of the competition to ensure prizes can be delivered to winning site users.

If you use one of our personalised Tots100 badges (using the code provided in your Tots100 account) then we will record the number of requests for this image from your site. This information will be used to form part of your Tots100 ranking, and will not involve collecting any personal data from which any individual could be identified. If you prefer not to use the personalised badge, there are alternative badges available [elsewhere on the site](https://www.tots100.co.uk/get-your-tots100-badges-here/).

Flea Enterprises Ltd is not responsible for the web sites that are referred to or linked to from this website. When you visit these web sites your personal information might be used in ways that do not conform to this policy.

**Information for Subscribers  **

If you pay for any service from Flea Enterprises Ltd, please note we do not store credit card details nor do we share customer details with any 3rd parties.

When you subscribe to our service, your account will be activated within 48 hours of payment being received, and you will receive a log-in for your account to your nominated email address.  If you do not receive a log-in or have any questions about how to use your log-in credentials, please contact us at admin@fleaenterprises.com or on 01253 739 408.

For further information, please see our [terms and conditions ](https://www.tots100.co.uk/terms/)for brands.

**Cookies**

When you visit the Tots100 or any Flea Enterprises website, we use “cookie” technology to improve your experience of the website. Cookies are small pieces of information that are issued to your computer or browsing device, which store information about your use of the website.

Most cookies used on this site last only for the duration of your web session and will expire when you close your browser. Other cookies are used to remember your account details when you return to the website and may last for longer.

**Flea Enterprises use cookies to:**

• create a specific log-in session for a visitor to the Tots100 website in order that services are delivered in an effective, secure and consistent manner;  
• recognise when a visitor to the Tots100 website has visited before; this means we can identify the number of unique visitors we receive to the website;  
• collect statistical information about how our visitors use the website so that we can improve the website and learn which parts are most popular to visitors; and

Most web browsers automatically accept cookies but, if you prefer, you can change your browser to prevent that or to notify you each time a cookie is set. You can also learn more about cookies by visiting www.allaboutcookies.org which includes additional useful information on cookies and how to block cookies using different types of browser.

Please note that by blocking or deleting cookies used on a Flea Enterprises Ltd website you may lose access to some of the functionality of the website.

**Feedback, Comments & Suggestions**

If you have any queries about our privacy and cookies policy, please do not hesitate to contact us. Our address is Flea Enterprises Ltd, 3a Clifton Square, Lytham St. Annes, Lancashire, FY8 5JP

**Finally**

If you do not agree with this Privacy Policy you should not submit your personal information on this website. Please refer to the site’s [Terms and Conditions](https://www.tots100.co.uk/terms/)

_Last updated: 1 March, 2013  _
